https://faithandfitness.net/privacy-policy/

Personal information
If you contact us via this website via the contact form or by registering for the mailing list, we will collect the email address you nominate and any other identifying information you provide, such as a name, address or phone number. This information is collected and used for the purposes of Faith and Fitness contacting you. Your information is collected and stored securely and is never passed on to other 3rd parties without your permission.
For each visitor to reach the site, we expressively collect the following non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to browser type, version and language, operating system, pages viewed while browsing the Site, page access times and referring website address. This collected information is used solely internally for the purpose of gauging visitor traffic, trends and delivering personalized content to you while you are at this site.
Our website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. When you go to other websites from here, we advise you to be aware and read their privacy policy.
We also integrate with social media sites such as Facebook, Instagram, Twitter and others. If you choose to “like” or “share” information from this website through these services, you should review the privacy policy of that service. If you are a member of a social media site, the interfaces may allow the social media site to connect your visits to this site with other personal information.
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will use for these new purposes only, data collected from the time of the policy change forward will adhere to our updated practices.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to make amendments to this Privacy Policy at any time. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Site.
Accessing Your Personal Information
You have a right to access your personal information, subject to exceptions allowed by law. If you would like to do so, please let us know. You may be required to put your request in writing for security reasons.
Contact Us
We welcome your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and would like further information, please contact us via the contact form on this website.
Current Issue
Read MoreChurch
College
Culture
Family Fitness
Men
Nutrition
Training
Your couch. It is mine.
Form goes here
Form goes here
